(Raj:)You own the damn thing,
just take a freaking sweater.
(Sheldon:)I didn't turn a profit last quarter...
(Sheldon:)...by taking product off the shelves
willy-nilly.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Raj:)You've paid for a sweater
and you're in Sheldon Square.
Ahem. Hang on.
(Sheldon:)It's a cardigan, I have to button it.
(Sheldon:)-Oh, no.
-What now?
(Sheldon:)A Godzilla-like monster
is approaching the city.
(Sheldon:)I have to get my people to safety.
(Sheldon:)People of Sheldonopolis,
this is your mayor.
(Sheldon:)Follow me.
(Sheldon:)If the children can't run,
leave them behind.
(Sheldon:)Oh, the simulated horror.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Sheldon:)Raj?
[SIGHS]
(Sheldon:)Just as I suspected.
(Sheldon:)Meditation is nothing but hokum.